now I'm going to read some sentences and you have to touch the picture that corresponds the image
and move images that you were used
ok?
in this example if I said the boy sits, when you would touch the sitting boy...
ok? ready
the boy holds the girl
the girl holds the boy
he holds him
he holds her
she holds him
the father washes her son
the mother washes her daughter
he washes him
he washes himself
she washes herself
she washes her
the boy hold the girls
he holds him
he holds her
she hold them
the girl pushes the boy
the boy pushes the girl
the boy's pushed by the girl
the girl's pushed by the boy
it's the boy who pushes the girl
it's the girl who pushes the boy
it's the boy the girl pushes
it's the girl the boy pushes
the dog bites the cat
the cat bites the dog
the dog is bitten by the cat
the cat is bitten by the dog
it's the dog that bites the cat
it's the cat that bites the dog
it's the cat the dog bites
it's the dog that the cat bites
the truck pulls the car
the car's pulled by the truck
the truck is pulled by the car
the car pulls the truck
it's the truck that pulls the car
it's the car the truck pulls
it's the car that pulls truck
it's the truck the car pulls
the mother dresses her daughter
the father dresses her son
she dresses herself
she dresses him
she dresses her
he dressed himself
the girl doesn't push the boy
the boy doesn't push the girl
the girl's not pushed by the boy
the boy's not pushed by the girl
the girl doesn't spray the boy
the boy doesn't spray the girl
the girl is sprayed by the boy
I'm uh.. one late
yeah
so, the boy is not sprayed by the girl
is not sprayed by the girl?
uh-huh
the girl's not sprayed by the boy
the girl's sprayed by the boy
it's still there?
yeah
the girl's sprayed by the boy
the boy's not near* the girl
the truck doesn't pull the car
the truck is not pulled by the car
the car is not* pulled the truck
the car is not pulled by the truck
the young boy doesn't wake up his mother
the mother doesn't wake up the young boy
the young boy is not woken up by his mother
the mother is not waking up by the young boy
the dog isn't bit by the cat
the cat is not bitten by the dog
the dog doesn't bite the cat
the cat doesnt bite the dog
the man doesn't kiss the woman
the woman is not kissed by the man
the woman doesn't kiss the man
the man is not kissed by the woman
touch the mother's baby
touch the niece's uncle
touch the base of the flower
show me the manager of the restaurant
show me the book of this author
show me the master's dog
show me the patient's doctor
show me the director of the film
show me the baby's mother
show me the niece's uncle
show me the flower of the base*
show me the restaurant manger
show me the author of the book
show me the master's dog
show me the patient's doctor
show me the film director